intercreditreport.com 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy

##  Introduction

We are determined to protect your privacy. This privacy policy clearly outlines how we processes your personal data and your rights in relation to each data processed. We recommend you carefully read through this document to learn more about our Privacy Policy. 

In this Privacy Policy, the following definitions are adopted: 

·               "Us", "We", "Our" the data controller of your personal data and is subject to any locally applicable data protection laws in the USA and other regulations such as· General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR").of EU. 

·               "You", "Your", "Yours" means you, the data subject. 

This Privacy Policy supersedes any previous Privacy Policy which you may have been provided with. 

This Privacy Policy governs us and ours online websites, products, and services. We are not responsible or liable for any privacy issues of any third-party websites we may be linking to. We urge you to be careful when providing personal data to outside parties. 

##  Who we are and what we do

We are an aggregator of corporate data from both public and private sources and maintain a database of over millions companies that covers US states. 

We offers business checking facilities and helping users make better financial decisions and minimise business risk. In order for us to provide this service, we are required to collect, process, and store data on companies and their historical conduct. This data comprises of information on a corporate level such as company name, company address, financial accounts, and information on an individual basis such as directors, people of significant control and shareholders. 

##  Types of personal data we collect 

This sections explains all the different types of personal information We collects, processes and stores. They are grouped together as follows: 

Type of personal data

| 

Description  
  
---|---  
  
Identity Data

| 

This comprises of data used to identify you (many of this data will be provided by you) and so includes name, title, age and date of birth.   
  
Contact Data

| 

This consists of data used to contact you such has your home address, email address and telephone number.   
  
Financial

| 

This data will be provided by you when purchasing our products such as your credit/debit card and bank account details. We will not store your full credit/debit card details in its database (this is handled by our payment processor).   
  
Transactional

| 

Details about payments to and from us and information on products and services you may have purchased and vouchers or coupons you may have used during your purchase.   
  
Technical

| 

Details on the software, devices and technology you used when accessing our websites such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version.   
  
Usage Data

| 

This consists of data on how you use We's website, products and services.   
  
Subjects of users interests 

| 

Subjects of your interests to precisely publish ads   
  
Consents

| 

Details of any permissions, consents or preferences that you give We such as how you wish to be contactd or other marketing and communications choices.   
  
##   

##  Personal data we don't collect 

We does not collect or process any "sensitive personal data" or other "special category data". Examples would include information relating to ethnicity and political or religious beliefs. In addition to this, We does not collect or process data relating to any persons under 16 years of age. 

##  Personal data we collect and how we collect it 

This section lists all the ways We collects personal data. 

1.       Provided by you

From time to time, We will collect and store information provided by you, such as: 

·               Updating yourcompanyinformation

·               Creating a support ticket or help request

·               Reporting issues with our website or products

·               When purchasing a product or service

The personal data you provide may be personally identifiable but do not fall under the sensitive data category as defined by GDPR and other regulations. 

We may ask for any of the following information: 

·               Your name including first name(s) and surname

·               Your email address

·               Your home or business address

·               Your telephone number

·               Third party social profiles such as Facebook and Twitter

·               Debit or Credit Card details including the name displayed across your card 

2.       As you use our products and services

As you interact with us, the platform will automatically collect information about your browser, internet and device, which we use to improve our products and services. Many of this data cannot be used to directly identify you, such as: 

·               Device information including browser type, settings and operating system 

·               Details of how you used our service, such as your navigation history 

·               Device language, the date and time of your requests and referral pages 

·               Your IP address (this is not directly identifiable but may be indirectly) 

·               Subjects of your interest

·                

3.       From outside organisations and publicly available sources

In order for us to provide business products and services, it is required to collect and aggregate both commercial and personal data from a number of sources. This includes both publicly available sources such as DOSs ·and outside organisations. We may also collect personal data from outside sources for legal reasons such as regulatory obligations. 

We collects data from a number of external sources, such as: 

·               DOS and other suppliers. We receives personal data from suppliers including particulars of company directors, secretaries, shareholders and people with significant control. 

·               Personal information including credit information, from private third party sources such as: 

·                     Credit reference agencies

·                     Business directories

·                     Company list brokers

·                     Fraud prevention agencies

·                     Government and law enforcement agencies

·               Website usage data from analytics providers such as Google Analytics 

·               Information found on websites in the public domain

##  How we store your personal data 

Your personal data is stored in· data centre. The data centre has a number of security features in place to protect your personal data such as: 

·               A secure location with physical security such as card and pin entrance barriers with 24/7 manned and patrolled external security. 

·               Independent infrared CCTV surveillance and centrally controlled access systems with complete logs of personnel entrances and exits. 

·               All network inbound and outbound are protected by the latest firewall and software technology. 

##  How long we store your personal data for 

We will only store and process your personal data for as long as it has a lawful basis to do so and will make sure your privacy is protected. A few reasons why we will store your personal data in particular are: 

·               Purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. 

·               We are required by law to retain basic information about our customers for 6 years after they cease being customers for tax and legal purposes. 

In some circumstances you can ask us to erase your data. See the "Your rights" section for more information. 

##  How we share your personal data 

We collects business information from third parties , which may include personal data, for the purposes of providing business products and services. We may share your this data with outside organisations such as service providers and regulators. This section lists the different types of organisations we may share your personal data with. 

·               Cliens and suppliers with whom we enters into an agreement with to provide business information or commercial data. 

·               Regulators or law enforcement agencies where we is required to do so. 

·               Professional advisers where it is necessary for us to obtain their advice or assistance, including lawyers, accountants, IT or public relations advisers. 

·               Debt collection agencies where it is necessary for us to recover money. 

·               Payment processing agents where it is necessary for us to protect a transaction. 

·               With third parties and their advisers where those third parties are acquiring, or considering acquiring, all or part of us. 

We will not disclose or sell your personal data which you have provided to us by means of explicit consent to clients or marketing agencies. 

##  Transferring your personal data outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") if you are a resident of EEA 

If you are resident of EEA in certain circumstances we may share your personal data with third parties situated in countries outside the EEA. When we transfers your personal data out of the EEA, it will ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it, by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented: 

·               The country that we send the personal data to is approved by the European Commission as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data 

·               The transfer is to a recipient in the United States of America who has registered under the EU/US Privacy Shield 

·               The recipient has entered into European Commission standard contractual clauses with us 

·               You have explicitly consented to the transfer of your personal data 

##  Your rights

This section explains your rights on how we collects, processes and stores your personal data. 

Your rights under data protection laws, in relation to your personal data are: 

·               Right of access to your personal data or commonly known as "data subject access request". This right entitles you to receive a copy of the personal data which we store about you and details on how we are processing it. 

·               Right to rectification entitles you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected. It is important to note that before we make any amendments to your personal data, we may need to verify the accuracy of any new information you provide us. 

·               Right to erasure of your personal data or commonly known as "the right to be forgotten". This right entitles you to request to delete or remove your personal data, where there is no lawful basis for us to continue to process it. You also have the right to request to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing, where we may have processed your information unlawfully, or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. We may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific reasons which will be notified to you at the time of your request. 

·               Right to object to the processing of your personal data. This right entitles you to object if you feel our processing of your personal data affects your fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your personal data which override your rights and freedoms. You have an absolute right to object to the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. 

·               Right to restrict processing of your personal data. This right entitles you to suspend or restrict the processing of your personal data in the following circumstances: 

·                     You want us to establish the data's accuracy

·                     Where we are unlawfully processing your personal data and you do not want us to erase it 

·                     Where you need us to hold the data, even if we are no longer processing it, as you need it to establish, exercise or defend a legal claim. 

·                     You have objected to our processing of your personal data, but we need to establish whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to process it. 

·               Right to data portability of your personal data. This right entitles you to request to have your personal data transferred to you or to a third party you have chosen. We will provide the personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. This right only applies to personal data which you initially provided consent or where we processed the information to perform a contract with you. 

·               Right to withdraw consent at any time to the processing of your personal data, where we are relying on consent as our lawful basis. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will inform you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent. 

If you wish to exercise any of your rights mentioned above, please contact us. 

##  Updating your personal data

You have the right to amend any personal data we has about you that you think is incorrect or incomplete. We'll take the necessary steps to verify any incorrect data and correct it where possible. 

##  If you choose not to give your personal data 

You are within your rights to refuse to give us any of your personal data, however this can have negative effects on how we can serve you as a customer, such as: 

·               We may not be able enter into or fulfil a contract we have or trying to have with you 

·               We may not be able to offer propositions or quotations on our products and services 

·               We may have to cancel any existing products or service you have with us 

From time to time, we may ask you for personal data that is useful but not required by law or in order to enter into a contract. We will clearly explain to you when it is optional to provide a particular data. The service or product we provides to you won't be affected if you choose not to provide any optional personal data. 

##  How to withdraw your consent

You can withdraw your consent at any time to the processing of your personal data. Please contact us· if you wish to withdraw consent. This will only affect the way we process your personal data where our reason for doing so is that we have your consent. 

##  Marketing

From time to time, we may send you marketing materials about products and services it provides which it believes may be of interest to you. In addition to this, we may also send other information in the form of alerts, surveys, newsletters and invitations to events or functions which it believes might be of interest to you or in order to update you with information you have requested. 

We will communicate this to you in a number of ways including by post, telephone, email or other digital channels. We can only use your personal information to send you marketing material if it has either your consent or a legitimate interest. It must not conflict unfairly with your own interests. 

If you object to receiving marketing from us at any time, please contact us. 

##   

##   

##   

##  How to complain

Please get in touch with us if you are unhappy with how we have used your personal data. 

##  Contacting us

You may contact us about any of the topics set out in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or want more details about how we use your personal data, or wish to excercise your rights, you can contact us using our online contact. 

You may also email us directly at helpdesk at support@intercreditreport.com. Please note at this time we do not offer telephone support for enquiries regarding your personal data and privacy concerns. 

##  Frequently Asked Questions

This section provides answers to the most frequently asked questions regarding your privacy and personal data. 

What personal data does you have about me? 

The personal data that we has about you will include personal data you have provided to us and personal data we may have collected about you from third party sources. If you are connected to a legal entity such as a public company, we will store personal data about you in relation to that legal entity such as company director and shareholder information. 

I haven't given my consent or permission for you to process my personal data 

We processes a portion of your personal data based on your explicit consent. You give us your consent when we ask for personal data such as your name and you provide this to us usually through an online form. 

We processes other personal data based on our legitimate interest, that is to provide services and products in the public's interest which help them meet with compliance and legal obligations, protect them against fraud, reduce financial risks by having comprehensive information on individuals and corporate entities, and provide marketing solutions to help them grow their business. 

I want· to erase all personal data you have about me 

We will erase personal data that you have explicitly consented, that is personal data that you have provided to us. You may withdraw your consent at any time. If you wish to withdraw your consent, please contact.  
As for personal data which you haven't explicitly consented, we has legitimate grounds to gather and process this personal data in accordance with the regulations, such as the GDPR on other ones. If you feel the processing of your personal data impacts your rights and freedoms, please contact us. 

According to the regulations such as GDPR, when does my right to erasure not apply? 

Your right to erasure does not apply if processing is necessary for one of the following reasons: 

·               To exercise the right of freedom of expression and information

·               To comply with a legal obligation

·               For the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority 

·               For archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific research historical research or statistical purposes where erasure is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of that processing 

·               For the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

How do I remove my information from public search engines? 

You may request to have your information removed from search engines.  Please complete  the  Contact Form .
